[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 33]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
“Unsoiled Starlight” ]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
Go with Daddy.
Bye-bye.
Oh, teacher.
I'm here to pick up Xiao He.
Nianhe?
Nianhe was already picked up by her uncle.
He just left not long ago.
Okay.
Thank you. I got it.
Hello?
Yi Muyang.
You should be resting. Why did you
pick up Xiao He again?
where did you take Xiao He
Where did you two go?
I've been wronged!
My dad was watching. I really didn't
go anywhere today.
I really didn't go anywhere today.
Then where's Xiao He?
Is Xiao He missing?
[Delicious ice cream] [Second half price]
Xiao He.
You're so little—
can you really eat ice cream?
Of course.
I want blueberry flavor.
Is it good?
Mm.
Shu Nianhe.
[Delicious ice cream] [Second half price]
What did Mom tell you?
Don't casually eat things
strangers give you.
And never casually go with strangers.
But Mom, you know Uncle Zhuo.
That still doesn't make it okay.
Only people you're very close to
can be trusted.
But Mom,
you often look at Uncle Zhuo's photos.
Does that count as close?
What?
Backpack.
Mr. Zhuo, what does this mean?
Trying to use personal connections
to influence my work decisions?
It really was just a coincidence
that I picked her up.
Xiao He had been waiting at
the teacher's place for a long time,
so I brought her out.
No matter what,
Zhuo Yu'an,
don't drag my child
into whatever is between us.
Xiao He,
are you okay?
Uncle Zhuo,
thank you.
Are you okay?
Wow.
It hurts so much.
My—
why is my shoulder starting to hurt again?
That's enough.
Stop acting.
Hey, Tinglan.
You used to care about me so much.
If I got even a tiny injury,
you'd bandage it for me yourself.
You said it yourself—that was before.
Shu Nianhe, sit properly.
I've taken Zhuoyuan Tech's case.
Lawyer Sun is right.
Since I don't have experience
winning cases,
and this case is
highly watched in the industry,
there's no reason not to take it.
As for Mr. Zhuo's work principles,
I will strictly abide by them.
I hope Mr. Zhuo will too.
Ouch.
It still hurts so much.
[Outpatient]
Are you alright now?
What did the doctor say?
If there's nothing else,
I'll take Xiao He home first.
Tinglan.
I still have a project procedure
to go over with you.
Now?
Mm.
Yes.
Tinglan.
Grandpa.
Hey.
Little darling Nianhe.
Tinglan, give me a hand.
Uncle Yi.
How's your health lately?
Great!
I've already pushed this kid
around the ward in a big circle.
Not even out of breath.
Tinglan,
I told you I'm fine.
No need to come to the hospital to see me.
Mr. Zhuo got hurt.
We took him to get it treated.
What happened to Mr. Zhuo?
Even a CEO gets hurt?
I accidentally scratched myself.
Tinglan was worried about me
and insisted on coming along while
I got bandaged.
That's our Tinglan.
Whether it's family
or colleagues,
she's equally kind and warm-hearted.
Naturally.
Tinglan,
I feel like my
arm still hurts a bit.
Did the doctor just say
I need another X-ray?
Why is my leg starting to hurt too?
It's fine, Tinglan.
You go with Mr. Zhuo first.
I—
I might be used to it.
Tinglan,
I think I have low blood sugar.
What's going on?
Tinglan.
Then it's really been tough on you.
Every day you have to take care of
the frail and sickly
and irrelevant people.
Teacher said
kids who behave well
can get a little red flower as a reward.
I'll give you my little red flower.
Pain, fly away.
Thank you.
Thank you, Nianhe.
Pain, fly away.
Alright, alright.
How old are you all?
Still playing these childish tricks.
I'll push him back first.
Bye, Grandpa.
Bye, Nianhe.
Okay.
You—
stop always doing these things
that put others in awkward positions.
That's not how you win a girl over.
If there's nothing else,
I'll take Xiao He and go first.
Tinglan.
I remember
Nianhe's kindergarten
is holding a parent-child sports day.
I don't think there is no
any suitable person to attend.
So how about I go in their place—
Don't even think about it.
[Hua'an City Zhihang Kindergarten]
School's out!
Xiao He.
Want me to take you to the pet store?
Okay.
Let's go.
Forgot what you promised again.
[Puff Pets]
[Open]
Xiao He.
Do you like it?
I like it.
Thank you, Uncle, for bringing me
to see the puppies.
Let me tell Uncle a secret.
Okay.
Uncle knows.
So, shall we go in and take a look?
But I still need to ask Mom first.
Shu Nianhe.
[Open]
You still remember you need to ask me?
Mom.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I really can't do anything about you.
[Open]
Xiao He is young, so fine.
But Zhuo Yu'an,
you're ignoring my words too?
You spoil her every day,
spoiling her wild.
Xiao He won't be wild.
Backpack.
Let's go.
Shu Tinglan.
Can you give me
a way to contact you?
I don't want to have to use the work email
every time I look for you.
With your capability,
you can find it
without me giving it to you.
Let's go.
Xiao He, let's go home.